(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T22:56:13.621383",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
3D Birthday LIVE 2026 - THE ONE & ONLY
Hey everybody!
Today I would like to introduce you...
...to the one and only entertainer!
Ready, go!
Go!
始まった show time
Showtime has begun,
鳴り響く歓声
cheers echoing all around!
(Let's get up, get up, get up)
Oh ジャンガジャンガ
Oh, jangajanga,
心 踊らせ
make your heart dance!
(Let's get up, get up, get up)
指を鳴らせば 変わる景色が
Snap your fingers, and the scenery changes.
退屈な街でも ほら ブロードウェイ
Even a boring town becomes Broadway, see!
今宵の主役は 私よ
Tonight's main star is me!
1, 2, Let's go! 3, 4!
It's my showtime!
Let the show begin 最高のショー
Let the show begin! The greatest show,
楽しみましょう！
let's enjoy it!
一度きりの人生なの
You only live once,
ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン yeah
darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事も いざ 東雲よ
Love and work, let's head for the dawn!
1, 2, 3, 4, Hah!!
Let the show begin
照らす Moon light
Illuminated by the moonlight,
スポットライトにして
turning it into a spotlight,
(Let's get up, get up, get up)
Oh ラタータッタッ
Oh, ratatatta,
軽快なステップで
with light steps!
(Let's get up, get up, get up)
音を鳴らせば 拍手の渦が
When the music plays, a wave of applause
轟く スタンディングオベーション
roars into a standing ovation!
今宵の主役に あなたも
Tonight, you too can be the main star!
1, 2, Let's go! 3, 4!
It's our showtime!
Let the show begin 最高のショー
Let the show begin! The greatest show,
楽しみましょう！
let's enjoy it!
一度きりの人生なの
You only live once,
ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン yeah
darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事も いざ 東雲よ
Love and work, let's head for the dawn!
1, 2, 3, 4, Hah!!
Let the show begin
Come on, trombone!
Do it naughty, everybody come follow me, yeah
Be scandalous 今にも
Be scandalous, even right now!
Let's do it very, very, very bad
So beautiful 何度でも
So beautiful, time and time again!
Let's do it very, very, very bad
So beautiful
何度でも
Time and time again
Let's go away, Very Very Very Very
Let the show begin あなたも 燃え尽きましょう
Let the show begin, let's burn out together!
一度きりの人生でしょう
You only live once, right?
Darling Darling Darling Yeah
恋も 仕事も いいだろ 私のために
Love or work, it's fine, all for my sake
1 2 3 4 Huh
Let's show begin
Let the show begin 最高 Showtime
Let the show begin, the ultimate showtime
楽しみたいでしょう
You want to enjoy it, don't you?
一度きりの人生なのだ
Because you only live once
Darling Darling Darling Yeah
恋も 仕事も いいだろ 私のために
Love or work, it's fine, all for my sake
1 2 3 4 Huh
This is my showtime
Come on
Be Naked
[Title: Be Naked]
Unbreaking な抵抗 罠に 他の誰でもないの Me
Unbreaking resistance in a trap, it's nobody else but Me
君の願いも簡単に 叶えたから Lock in on me
I easily granted your wish, so lock in on me
Break it 掴んだ 嘘だらけの世界とは Break up
Break it, seized it, break up with this world of lies
I wish 伸びた ありのままで 越えてく Future
I wish, reaching out, overcoming the future as I am
見せつける ありのまま Addict in night
Showing off as I am, addict in night
Reset なんて 間違わない Addict in night
No mistake in resetting, addict in night
こだわる My style 幾度もない 越えてく My guideline
Sticking to my style, rare chances, crossing my guideline
Now judge it my life 見せるだけ 振り向かない
Now judge my life, just showing it, never looking back
見せかけの Luxury
Superficial luxury
魅せる 魅せる 抜け出すの My way
Charming, charming, breaking out my way
見せつける Ecstasy
Showing off ecstasy
Don't be afraid, I don't care だから Go my way
Don't be afraid, I don't care, so go my way
Show me what's after future
Be naked Be naked Be naked 全望むまま Get it
Be naked, Be naked, Be naked, get everything as desired
Be naked Be naked Be naked Show me what's after future
Do you understand?
With unnaked 欲望も 望むまま Get it
With unnaked, even desires, get them as wished
脳にも Noise 見えぬ摩天楼
Noise in the brain, unseen skyscrapers
With unnaked あの日から 遠慮はしない
With unnaked, since that day I hold nothing back
手探り Hand 散々乱暴
Groping hand, terribly wild
惑わせる Fantasy
Bewitching fantasy
ミスに 騙されはしないの
I won't be fooled by mistakes
幕開ける Binary
Unveiling the binary
Are you okay? I'm okay だから Don't be sad
Are you okay? I'm okay, so don't be sad
Show me what's after future
Be naked Be naked Be naked 全望むまま Get it
Be naked, Be naked, Be naked, get everything as desired
Be naked Be naked Be naked Show me what's after future
自分隠すのは楽だよね
It's easy to hide yourself, isn't it?
周りに合せていればそれで
Just conforming to those around you
とりあえず一人にならずに済むから 笑えるの
Because at least you avoid being alone, it's laughable
本当はもう気づいて 歯車に 蠢いている
In truth you already noticed, squirming in the gears
なのに何で諦めてる もう一度確かめ
Yet why give up? Confirm it once more
始めましょう リアルな Show どこからでも 好きにどうぞ
Let's begin, a real show, feel free from anywhere
アイドに ハートに Show me what's after future
In eyes, in heart, show me what's after future
Hey, what you want, don't be, don't be shy
Hey, what you need, 大丈夫さ
Hey, what you need, it's alright
Hey, what you want, don't be, don't be shy
そのままで Get it on, yeah, it's true
Just as you are, get it on, yeah, it's true
Hey, what you want, don't be, don't be shy
Hey, what you need, 大丈夫さ
Hey, what you need, it's alright
Hey, what you want, don't be, don't be shy
そのままで Get it on, yeah, it's true
Just as you are, get it on, yeah, it's true
「ユルサナイ」
"I won't forgive you"
Loveit?
[Title: Loveit?]
ぞっとした顔が可愛いな
A horrified look on your face is so cute.
君のその体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
Love it? 何？
Love it? What?
割に合わない
It's just not worth it.
かわいそうね 君は
Poor thing, you are...
悪い子なの？
...such a bad kid, aren't you?
どの顔がお好きで ざにざに
Which face do you like? Zani, zani...
色目が お上手に出来たわき？
Making eyes at me so skillfully, huh?
君に躍らされちゃって 私は狂う
Led on a dance by you, I'm going crazy.
What is love it?
君の中まで 骨の髄まで
Deep inside you, to the very marrow of your bones...
容れてから 空っぽになる 愛のパペット
...filled up, then becoming empty—a puppet of love.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest tightens, doesn't it? You're suffocating, right?
それが恋と 教えてあげる あはは
I'll teach you that that is love, ahaha.
頭の空で ほら囁いて
Look, inside your empty head, whisper to me.
いい子ね 首輪付けた君は Love it?
Good boy... Wearing a collar, you're "Love it?"
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone completely crazy, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, you see.
したいようで してあげるわ 行って あはは
As if you want to... I'll do it for you, go on, ahaha.
塗れた君の赤い正義 汚れるまで
Until your wet, red justice gets stained...
大体の尊厳で生きて 死んでは生きるまで
...living with general dignity, until dying and living again.
愚かね 愚かね
How foolish, how foolish!
間抜けな顔して
Making such a stupid face...
君は悪い子なの？
...are you a bad kid?
痛いのがお好きで ざにざに
You like it when it hurts? Zani, zani...
あら お口はチャックで 何何？
Oh, zipper on your mouth? What's that, what's that?
踊らされちゃう君を 食う
I'll devour you as you're made to dance.
What is...
君の中まで 骨の髄まで
Deep inside you, to the very marrow of your bones...
貪り尽くせば もう空っぽのパペット
...if I devour you completely, you're already an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
Your chest tightens, doesn't it? You're suffocating, right?
それが恋と 教えてあげる あはは
I'll teach you that that is love, ahaha.
君はピエロね 愛を囁いて
You're a clown, aren't you? Whispering love...
人間の形して 君は Love it?
...in the shape of a human, you're "Love it?"
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone completely crazy, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, you see.
したいようで してあげるわ 行って あはは
As if you want to... I'll do it for you, go on, ahaha.
報い償い 穢れた体に溺れるまで
Retribution and atonement, until drowning in your defiled body...
大体の尊厳で息息が止まるまで
...living with general dignity, until your breath stops.
報い償い 穢れた体に溺れるまで
Retribution and atonement, until drowning in your defiled body...
大体の尊厳で息息が止まるまで
...living with general dignity, until your breath stops.
皆さん
Everyone!
本日は
Today...
伊咲リロナ 生誕祭 2026 に
Thank you so much for coming to...
遊びに来てくれて 本当にありがとうございます！
...Isaki Riona Birthday Fest 2026!
レッド・シャッフル、えーっと、ビニーきっと、Loveit? と3曲続けて披露させていただきました！
I performed 3 songs in a row: Red Shuffle, Um, Be Neatly, and Loveit?!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
改めて自己紹介させてください！
Let me introduce myself once again!
私のもとに おいで！ リロナインダステージ！
Come to me! Riona in the Stage!
PLUMPMONSTERのリーダー 伊咲リロナです！ プラプラー！ よろしくお願いします！
I'm Isaki Riona, the leader of PLUMPMONSTER! Plum-Plum! Nice to meet you!
はぁ、息切れが… 息切れがひどいんですけど、
Phew, I'm so out of breath... I'm really out of breath, but...
はい、今日のですね、ハッシュタグはこちら！
Yes! Today's hashtag is right here!
#伊咲リロナ生誕祭2026 です！
#IsakiRionaBirthdayFest2026!
たくさん、たくさん呟いてください！
Please tweet a lot, a whole lot!
私絶対に見に行くのでね！
Because I'm definitely going to check them out!
みんなが感想とかを送ってくれるの、すごく楽しみにしています！
I'm really looking forward to seeing everyone send their thoughts and comments!
そしてですね、本日ライブパフォーマンスさせていただくステージはこちらです！ どうですか？
And also, the stage where I'm performing live today is right here! What do you think?
ショーみたいでさ、めっちゃ良くない？
It looks like a real show, isn't it so cool?
あとね、伊咲リロナっていう名前がたくさん刻まれていたり、ハートの風船だったり、王冠だったり、
Plus, the name "Isaki Riona" is engraved all over, with heart balloons and crowns...
色んな装飾があって、とってもキラキラしてます！
There are so many decorations, making it super sparkly!
ここでね、踊れることが今日すごく、すごく幸せです！ ありがとうございます！
I feel so, so happy to be able to dance here today! Thank you so much!
そして、本日のライブのタイトルが「The One and Only」となっております！
And the title of today's live concert is "The One and Only"!
こちらの意味は「唯一無二」という意味です。
The meaning of this is "one and only" or "unrivaled".
このタイトルに恥じないように、全力で、全力でパフォーマンスしていくので、
To live up to this title, I'll perform with my absolute all, so...
どうかこの時間が、あなたの心に何か届けられる、そんな時間になれるように、今日は頑張りたいと思います！
...I'll do my best today so that this time spent together can deliver something special to your heart!
それでは次は、お待ちかねのゲストパートです！
Now then, next up is the eagerly awaited guest section!
どうぞ！
Here you go!
Blah Blah VIRTUAL Blah Blah
I'm a Vida
I'm a Vida La Vida La Vida Love
たかだかノーマライゼーション
It's mere normalization.
触らば可愛いのこと
Touch it, and it's something cute.
高天原からほら 脅してけ
Look, threaten them right from Takamagahara!
Hi, そう メメンヘラーでも 面言急なら 面キラ
Hi, that's right! Even if mental health is unstable, direct talk means face killer.
とか貼られたレッテル 狂ってるメンタルは
Stick on those labels, but this crazy mental state...
最強スマイルで 転がしてけ ぺんぺん
...roll with it using the ultimate smile, pen-pen!
ごまかしてる超新星に 晒されたら バイバイ
Exposed by a disguised supernova, then bye-bye.
にゃんてね
Just kidding!
I am a Vida I am a Vida
泡泡よ I am a Vida ラ・ヴィダ・ヴィダラワヤよ
It's pure bubbles! I am a Vida, La Vida Vidarawaya!
夢見てる少年
Boy who is dreaming,
夢見てる少女へ
girl who is dreaming...
Vida La Vida は 甘々甘々なの
...Vida La Vida is super sweet!
ガリガリガリ妄想 我を忘れるな
Crunching delusions, don't lose yourself!
我ら
We are...
センター 誰よりも駆け寄せ
Center, rushing over faster than anyone
パンダ 我々は誰だ
Panda, who are we?
まれに生んだ 自己愛性障害者
Unusually born narcissists
Am I... Am I Be...
Am I Be? Am I She? Am I Life? Am I She?
さらには 甘い 汁
On top of that, sweet juice
救いに 我愛你 So Love Me
To salvation, I love you, So Love Me
お出ましだ Hey Monster
Here comes Hey Monster
My name is... 愛でられたら墓場まで Laughter
My name is... if pampered, laughter all the way to the grave
Ama Beta 塗ったくった 心の中 Smooth like butter
Ama Beta, slathered on, inside my heart smooth like butter
Touch me 一体ならほら えんだら Catch me で ハイチーズ
Touch me, if as one, see, catch me and say cheese
召し上がる 墓はわからないが Wow 我理 心叫ぶ ひとつも Lifer
Enjoying it, though I don't know the grave, Wow my reason, heart screams, every single lifer
生きる姿や 魂を今
The living form and soul, right now
２つにして 愛をバラバラに
Split into two, scattering love to pieces
生まれた時の 喜びは
The joy from when we were born
肖像に さようならでいいな
Saying goodbye to portraits is fine
ダメね
No way
Wachawacha Wacha wa mecha mecha?
Wachawacha, is Wacha all messy?
楽観的な感性 あらら痛感で共感ね
An optimistic sensibility, oh my, empathy through deep feeling
怪態な正体ね あら
A strange true identity, oh my
Wachawacha Wacha wa mecha mecha?
Wachawacha, is Wacha all messy?
楽観的な感性 あらら痛感で共感ね
An optimistic sensibility, oh my, empathy through deep feeling
一巻の終わりだね
It's the end of the chapter
Ah, イミテーション
Ah, imitation
I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm a あわ あわ よ I'm a La Vida, I am Diva, Vida Nawaya yo
I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm a bubble, bubble, I'm a La Vida, I am Diva, Vida Nawaya
淫らは嫌 夢見てる少年 夢見てる少女へ
Lewdness is a no, to dreaming boys and dreaming girls
V な Vida は 甘 甘 甘 甘
A V-like Vida is sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet
とよ 昔 子供の頃 言われたもんだ
Long ago, when I was a child, I was told
あのヒーローショーの 人形の背中には
On the back of the dolls in that hero show
チャックはついてないから開くな
There's no zipper, so don't open it
バーチャルだ ヒューマンだ 詩のこの世が 存在は One-one だ
It's virtual, it's human, poetry's world, existence is one-on-one
惚れても死の Now バラバラな
Even if you fall in love, death's now scattered
VIRTUAL Blah Blah VIRTUAL Blah Blah
Are you ready for...
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall in love, you'll die
VIRTUAL Blah Blah VIRTUAL Blah Blah
Wacha wacha VIRTUAL Blah Blah
Umm, I'm a V
そら先輩！
Sora-senpai!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming!
一緒に歌えて嬉しかったね！
I was so happy we could sing together!
ねー！
Right!
そらりお！
SoraRio!
そらりおはファミリーだよー！
SoraRio is family!
Checkmate, I'm a superstar
Stay insane, but you rock with it
Like 24/7 I'm a hot mess ya love-hate
Get less boring, oh my god!
ホームラン バタバタ swing my shot
Home run, fluttering, swing my shot
Like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
英雄も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different
派手にぶちかませ
Go all out and blow them away
台詞通りのワイルドなスターティングローラー
A wild starting roller just like in the script
K.O. クリア Fly low あげる瞬間
K.O. clear, Fly low, the moment we turn it up
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
"Good vs. evil" is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party, just leave it to moi
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips
That's karma
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it
Sorry I'm just better
Sorry we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever
Whatever!
Talk about a "kumbaya"
Hey yeah, 正義のツラ フルスロットルぶちかまして
Hey yeah, with a face of justice, go full throttle and blow them away
欲望召し上がれ
Feasting on desires
アイ ドル吐き出せ We sing 叫ぶなら最高潮 Swag
Spit out idols, We sing, if you're gonna shout, peak Swag
Boom boom! 派手に
Boom boom! Flashy
Boom boom! ドラマチック
Boom boom! Dramatic
傷つき傷つけ人と この指止まれ
Hurting and getting hurt, people, come gather around
ハートにハートをハイにして 弾けて恥じらい捨てちゃい
Getting high heart to heart, bursting open and casting shame aside
叫び踊り誇れ 激動的ショータイム 酔いしれて頂戴
Shout, dance, and be proud, a turbulent showtime, get drunk on it please
同調のパラダイス
Paradise of synchronicity
惹かれ合う ガンガンガン 共鳴共鳴
Attracted to each other, bang bang bang, resonance resonance
"Good vs. evil, but I'm which one?"
Get less boring, oh my god!
What, ah!
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah, ah
That's karma, da da ha ha ha!
What, what, ah!
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it, yeah
That's karma, da da ha ha ha!
想像から 創造
From imagination to creation,
衝動から 欲望
from impulse to desire,
ほら 会ったように 華麗に演じる 劇的展開
look, dramatically performing gracefully as if met before.
毒毒し華
Poisonous flower,
Ya ya ya
暗い華
dark flower,
Ya ya ya
Sorry I'm just better
Sorry we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Betcha think you're clever
Ya ya ya
Whatever!
Talk about a kumbaya
Isekai queen
Switch チューニング マイナー
switch tuning minor,
カラフルな cacophony
colorful cacophony.
Ya ya ya!
It's Tuesday
優雅にハチャメチャ
elegantly chaotic.
Welcome to miss fortune's game
Ya ya ya, ya ya ya
カリオペ先輩、来てくれてありがとうございます！
Calliope-senpai, thank you so much for coming!
イエーイ！楽しかったー！
Yay! That was so much fun!
また歌いましょう！
Let me sing with you again! / Let's sing together again!
Let's sing together again!
歌いましょう！
Let me sing!
じゃあね〜！
Bye-bye~!
はあ…♡
Haa... ♡
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Doom Doom Doom)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Burn Burn)
Chu Chu Chu
Open Your Karte♡
Open Your Karte ♡
救助不可能
Impossible to rescue,
恋の病なの
it's love sickness.
どんどん熱を上げていく Virus
A virus continuously raising the fever,
Love me
危険な治療 試してみる？
Want to try a dangerous treatment?
飽くまで天使の優等生
Thoroughly an angel honor student,
Heaven in hell
ドキドキ動機は純粋
My thumping motivation is pure,
甘い曖昧乙女心
sweet, vague maiden heart.
どっち どっち
Which one, which one?
さあ 手の平の迷宮へようこそ
Come, welcome to the labyrinth in the palm of my hand.
「いい子だね♡」
“You're a good child ♡”
カルテNo. 運命の
Karte No., fate's
2 2 2 2
鳴り止まない
Unstopping
サイレン音が Wee Woo Woo Woo
siren sound goes Wee Woo Woo Woo.
好き？ 好き？ 速まる愛の心電図
Love? Love? An accelerating love EKG.
はい お薬をどうぞ♡
Here, have some medicine ♡
To to to U
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2-2-2-2 (Doom Doom Doom Doom)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Zoom)
Burn Burn Burn Chu Chu Chu
Open Your Karte♡
Open Your Karte ♡
二十四時間
Twenty-four hours,
呼吸困難
shortness of breath.
真っ赤な薔薇のトゲにキスして
Kiss the thorns of the crimson rose,
Kiss me
麻酔みたいな台詞
Words like anesthesia,
魔性の Babyface
devilish Babyface.
籠で飛び交う青い鳥
A blue bird flying in a cage,
Try & Error
ドクドク毒みたいな支配
Thumping, poison-like control,
笑顔に落下寸前 チクタク
on the verge of falling into a smile, tick-tock.
もう時間がない 秘密の正体
There's no more time, the secret true form.
「悪いこかも♡」
“Maybe I'm a bad child ♡”
カルテNo. 運命の
Karte No., fate's
2 2 2 2
追いつけない
Can't keep up
超スピードで Wee Woo Woo Woo
at super speed, Wee Woo Woo Woo.
好き？ 好き？ 乱れる愛の心電図
Love? Love? A disturbed love EKG.
もう 重症みたいです…
Looks like it's already critical condition...
Too Too Too Too Me♡
Too Too Too Too Me ♡
「先生、緊急事態です！」
“Doctor, it's an emergency!”
「カルテNo.2222の患者様です！」
“It's the patient of Karte No. 2222!”
「見てください！心電図がハートの形になっています！」
“Look! The EKG has turned into a heart shape!”
「もしもーし、聞こえますか？どこか痛いところはありますか？」
“Hello, can you hear me? Is there anywhere that hurts?”
「えっ？可愛すぎて胸が苦しい？息ができない！？」
“Eh? Your chest hurts because it's too cute? You can't breathe!?”
「もっと好きになっちゃうお注射しましょうね」
“Let's give you an injection that will make you fall in love more, okay?”
「大丈夫ですよー、ずっと私が手を握っていますからね」
“It's okay, I'll be holding your hand the whole time.”
「心拍数がどんどん上がっています！」
“The heart rate is rising rapidly!”
「わ！大変です！気を失っちゃったみたいです」
“Whoa, that's terrible! Looks like they fainted.”
「わたしの声聞こえますかー？」
“Can you hear my voice?”
「好きなところ言えますかー？」
“Can you tell us your favorite parts?”
「もうこうなったらあの手しかない！みんな離れて！」
“Since it's come to this, there's only that method! Everyone stand back!”
「あーあ だから言ったのに♡」
“Ah-ah, I told you so ♡”
カルテNo. さあ選んで 4 Card
Karte No., come choose a 4 Card.
裏表ツインテールの Joker
Double-sided twin-tail Joker.
Time over
…そう 神様さえ言う通り You're falling
...Yes, just as God says, You're falling.
…ぎゅっと結んだリボン
...Tightly tied ribbon,
誓いましょう 運命の警告が連なる暗示
let's vow, an omen where warnings of fate connect.
2 2 2
カルテNo. 運命の
Karte No., fate's
2 2 2 2
鳴り止まない
Unstopping
サイレン音が Wee Woo Woo Woo
siren sound goes Wee Woo Woo Woo.
好き？ 好き？ 速まる愛の心電図
Love? Love? An accelerating love EKG.
はい お薬をどうぞ♡
Here, have some medicine ♡
To to to U
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Doom Doom Doom)
2-2-2-2 (Zoom Zoom Zoom)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2-2-2-2 (Chu Chu Chu)
Open Your Karte♡
Open Your Karte ♡
見上げたあの夜空に
Looking up at that night sky,
浮かぶ星たち
the stars floating in it...
ふっと君の声が
Suddenly, I wondered if your voice...
あの頃輝いてたかな？
was shining back then?
今になっては
Now that time has passed,
ずっと分からないまま
I still don't know.
オーケストラ
[Orchestra]
あの時君がついた嘘
Back then, the lie you told...
問い糾せずに泣いたあの坂道
Without questioning it, I cried on that hill road.
この先君と会えないの
Can't I see you anymore from now on?
離れ離れに身を任せてた
I just surrendered to being apart.
いつもの後悔が風に消えてく
My usual regrets fade away in the wind.
誰にも見せないその姿を
That side of you that you show to no one else,
もうちょっとだけ見てたかったんだ
I just wanted to see it for a little longer.
時がそっと睨んでいる
Time is gently glaring at us.
その手と手繋いで
Holding those hands together,
笑い合った声忘れはしないよ
I'll never forget our voices laughing together.
こんなにも流してた涙も 語る声もオーケストラ
All these tears shed and our talking voices form an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
It eventually came, didn't it?
さよならの声
The voice saying goodbye.
忘れはしないよ
I will never forget it.
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
We were supposed to be so close,
今では繋がりなんてあの空だけ
but now our only connection is that sky.
夜空の交換をしよう
Let's exchange our night skies.
馬鹿らしくなって投げた午前3時
Feeling foolish, I gave up at 3:00 AM.
この先君と何年も
From now on, even as many years pass with you,
時の流れに身を任せても
even if I surrender to the flow of time...
いつものジョークが街に消えてく
The usual jokes fade away into the city.
誰にも見せない僕の姿を
A side of myself that I show to no one,
もうちょっとだけ見せたかったんだ
I just wanted to show you a little longer.
時がそっと睨んでいる
Time is gently glaring at us.
この目と目合わせはっきりしたい
I want to look eye to eye and make things clear.
もうできないのかな
Is that no longer possible?
こんなにもどかしくて辛いのが 音を立てるオーケストラ
This painful frustration making sound is an orchestra.
どこで何をしてるの？
Where and what are you doing?
分からないのは僕のせいなんだね
Not knowing is my fault, isn't it?
永遠にこんな日がくるなんて
That a day like this would come for eternity...
神様イタズラなら呪いたいぐらい
If it's God's prank, I want to curse it.
その手と手繋いで
Holding those hands together,
笑い合った声
the sound of our shared laughter...
忘れはしないよ
I will never forget.
こんなにも流してた涙も 語る声もオーケストラ
All these tears shed and our talking voices form an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
It eventually came, didn't it?
さよならの声
The voice saying goodbye.
これを知らないよ
I didn't even know this.
あなたにも近くにいた
I was supposed to be close to you,
はずが今では
but now, connected...
つながりなんて
...by nothing more than...
この空だけ
...this sky.
Wo-oh-oh...
Woah...
せーの！
Ready, set...
リオナお誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday, Riona!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
なんとFHGのみんなが来てくれました！ありがとう！
Everyone from FHG came over! Thank you!
やったー！ありがとう！おめでとう！
Yay! Thank you! Congratulations!
ついにね、初めての生誕ライブで、
Finally, my very first birthday live...
そしてFHGでね、こうやってライブできてすごく嬉しいよ！
and being able to perform live like this with FHG makes me so happy!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
エモかったね！エモかった？
That was emotional, right?
どうですか？エモかったですか？
How was it? Was it emotional?
泣いちゃったよ、リオナちゃん！
I almost cried, Riona-chan!
泣いちゃった？最高だよ！
You almost cried? That's awesome!
泣いちゃった？泣いちゃった？
Did you cry? Did you cry?
みんなとこうやってね、まあみんなの誕生日ライブがあるかどうか分かんないんだけど...
Being able to do this together... well, I don't know if everyone will have a birthday live, but...
え、どうだろね？ウチたちないの？
Wait, what? We don't have ones?
ウチらはサブだよ！
We're the sub-members, after all!
ねえ、リーダー！リーダー！
Hey, Leader! Put us in, Leader!
出させてくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for having us, Leader!
リーダー、本当に！
Leader, thank you so much!
まあまあ、リーダーとして言っておきまして...
So, as the Leader, I'm here to ask...
今日は！誕生日プレゼントにみんなからの超絶可愛い「おめでとう、リオナおめでとう！」っていうプレゼントが欲しいんだけど、いいかな？
Today, as a birthday present, I'd love to get a super cute "Congrats, Riona!" from all of you!
嫌です。
No way.
貰っていいですか？プレゼント！
Can I get it, please?
あざとい感じのやつ！
Give me that super cute, sweet kind of wish!
じゃあ「せーの」って言うから「リオナおめでとう」って言ってね。
Okay, when I say "Ready, set...", say "Congratulations, Riona!", okay?
プレゼントならしゃあないか。ちゃんと可愛くやれよ。
Well, if it's a present, guess we have to. Make it super cute!
任せろって！可愛くね！
Leave it to us! Cutely, right?
せーの！
Ready, set...
リオナ！おめでとう！
Riona! Congrats!
おい、待て待て！低い声はダメ！
Wait, wait! That deep voice is a no-go!
えー、ちょっとじゃあ見本見せてよ。初めての生誕ライブでしょ？
Come on, show us a proper example then! It's your first birthday live!
愛の言葉みたいなの！
Show us something like sweet words of love!
愛がいいよね！
Love is good, right?
セクシーで可愛く、愛！全身で！
Sexy, cute love! Do it full body!
いきますよ！3、2、1、はい！
Alright, here goes! Three, two, one, go!
今年もし、来年も、さ来年も、あなたに祝ってもらえますように！
This year, next year, and the year after... I hope you'll keep celebrating with me!
可愛い！
Cute!
ちょっと！恥ずかしい！
Wait, wait, that was awkward!
あなたはまだおい残りでーす。
Well, you still have some way to go.
んー...
Mmm...
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It felt like we were the only two people in this world.
なんて少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
I guess I was just dreaming for a little while.
爪先に月明かり 花束の香りに 指に触れる指
Moonlight on my toes, the scent of a bouquet, fingers touching fingers.
さよならもう行かなきゃ 何もかも忘れて
Goodbye, I must go now, forgetting everything.
硝子の上を裸足のまま歩く 痛むごとに血が流れて落ちていく
Walking barefoot over the glass, with every step of pain, blood flows and drips down.
お願いその赤い足跡を辿って会いに来て
Please, follow those red footprints and come see me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusty pool,
靴箱の中隠した林檎
an apple hidden inside a shoe locker,
萎びた君の肌に残る傷跡
scars remaining on your withered skin.
君のやうに 泳いだ迷子
A lost child swimming like you
どこにいる？ / どこにいるよ
Where are you? / I'm right here
何をして？ / ずっと見てるよ
What are you doing? / I'm always watching
この夜を間違いで満たそう / そばにいてよ
Let's fill this night with mistakes / Stay by my side
遊びに行こうよ
Let's go play
どこ見るの？
Where are you looking?
ガラスの指輪を 外しのまま歩く
Walking along, leaving my glass ring off
痛むごとに 血が流れて落ちていく
Every time it hurts, blood drips down
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints
会いに来て
Come see me
まるでこの世界で 2人だけみたいだね
It's as if there's only the two of us in this world
なんて 少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
...I was just dreaming for a little while
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
Morning on Yamate-dori stings my cheeks
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty pack of cigarettes
今日もまた足の踏み場は無い
Today again, there's no room to even step
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
My small room pampers my loneliness
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my ominous screams
未来等見ないで
Don't look to the future
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Overlay only the present you can be sure of
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call my name properly
身体を触って
Touch my body
必要なのは是だけ認めて
Acknowledge that this is all you need
愛してる 独り泣き叫んで
Saying "I love you," crying out loud alone
夜道を弄れど虚しい
Wandering through night streets, yet feeling empty
改札の安蛍光灯は
The cheap fluorescent lights at the ticket gate
貴方の影すら落とさない
Don't even cast your shadow
歪んだ無常の遠き日も
Even those distorted, transient distant days
セヴンスターの香り
Smell of Seven Stars
味わう如く季節を呼び起こす
Evoking the seasons as if savoring them
あたしが望んだこと自体
The very fact that I wished for it
矛盾を優に超えて
Far surpasses any contradiction
一番愛しいあなたの声迄
Even your most beloved voice
掠れさせて居たのだろう
Must have been made raspy by me
静寂を...
The silence...
サイレン
Siren
爆音
Roar of an engine
現実界
The real world
或る浮遊
A certain floating...
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my restless shrieking,
未来等見ないで
don't look to the future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just live in the moment, something you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body.
必要なのは是だけ認めて
All I need is this: acknowledge me.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my restless shrieking.
確信出来る
Just live in the moment,
現在だけ重ねて
something you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body.
必要なのは是だけ認めて
All I need is this: acknowledge me.
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
Yamate Street in the morning stings my cheeks.
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty pack of cigarettes.
今日もまた足の踏み場は無い
Today again, there's no room to take a step.
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
This tiny room indulges my loneliness.
タラタララ...
Tara tara ra...
ああ...
Ah...
ねえ、あんた分かっちゃいない！
Hey, you really don't get it!
阿修羅ちゃん
[Ashura-chan]
誰それがお手元の世界に夢中
Everyone's obsessed with the world in their hands,
化け物の飼い方を学んでる
learning how to tame a monster.
選ばれる為なら舌を売る
You'd sell your own tongue to get chosen,
裏切られた分だけ墓を掘る
digging as many graves as you've been betrayed.
へらへらのおつむがどうにかして
A brainless fool trying its best,
薄ら寒い言葉ばかりになる
overflowing with cringe-worthy words.
覚えない顔とバイバイできるなら
If I can say goodbye to faces I won't remember,
阿修羅にだってなれるわ
I could even become an Ashura.
逃げるえすけーぷ えすけーぷ えすけーぷ 仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape, remaining Buddha.
飛べるすてっぷ すてっぷ すてっぷ 仰せのまま
I can fly, step, step, step, as you command.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
どーどー閻魔様さえ喰らって
Even the Lord Enma can be devoured.
騙すすにーく すにーく すにーく 嵐の中
Deceive, sneak, sneak, sneak through the storm.
跳ねるすきっぷ すきっぷ すきっぷ あっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip. Oh really? Who cares!
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Might as well bleed them dry to the bone.
ねえ、あんた分かっちゃいない！
Hey, you really don't get it!
日々の滲みを木々にくべて暖をとりあう
Burning the oozing bits of daily life to stay warm,
義理を説いた彼の四肢は散り散りになる
the four limbs of he who preached duty are torn apart.
知りもせずに意味を美意識だと崇める
Without knowing, worshipping meaning as aesthetics,
擬似餌じみた慇懃にごの字だった
delighted by polite courtesy like a fake lure.
愉快な御託のフルコースに
A delightful full course of empty preaching,
上辺の面をして可愛がった
showed superficial affection.
くだらない僧と踊るくらいなら
If I have to dance with a good-for-nothing priest,
悪魔と手繋ぐわ
I'd rather hold hands with the devil!
逃げるえすけーぷ えすけーぷ えすけーぷ 仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape, remaining Buddha.
飛べるすてっぷ すてっぷ すてっぷ 仰せのまま
I can fly, step, step, step, as you command.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
阿鼻地獄の果てまでロックオン
Lock-on all the way to the end of Avici hell!
騙すすにーく すにーく すにーく 嵐の中
Deceive, sneak, sneak, sneak through the storm.
跳ねるすきっぷ すきっぷ すきっぷ あっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip. Oh really? Who cares!
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
あんた寝言はあの世で言って
Save your silly talk for the afterlife!
逃げるえすけーぷ えすけーぷ えすけーぷ 仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape, remaining Buddha.
飛べるすてっぷ すてっぷ すてっぷ 仰せのまま
I can fly, step, step, step, as you command.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Might as well bleed them dry to the bone!
ねえ、ギャーギャー言っちゃって！
Hey, squawking so loudly!
ああー！ 頭を垂れないで！
Ah! Don't hang your head!
ありがとうございます！ みんな、ありがとう！
Thank you so much! Thank you, everyone!
あ、やばい。ちょっと息が... お水飲ませてくださいね。すみませんね。
Ah, oh no. I'm a bit out of breath... Let me drink some water. Sorry about that.
あー、美味い！ すみません、お待たせしました。
Ah, that hits the spot! Sorry to keep you waiting.
先ほどは『ジェンドゥ』と『罪と罰』と『阿修羅ちゃん』をお届けしました！ いかがでしたでしょうか？
Earlier, I performed 'Jand', 'Crime and Punishment', and 'Ashura-chan'! How did you like them?
この後も、まだまだライブは続きます！
The live show will continue after this!
まだ披露してない、あんな曲や、こんな曲が、あるかもね！
There might still be that song or this song that I haven't performed yet!
なので、チャンネルはそのままで、まだ見ててくれたら嬉しいです！
So please stay tuned and keep watching! I'd be so happy!
ここでみんなにお知らせをさせてください！ こちらです！
Now, please let me make an announcement to everyone! Here it is!
伊咲リオナ 誕生日記念 2026のグッズが出ます！ やったー！
Isaki Riona Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise is coming out! Yay!
では、詳細を見ていきましょう！ まずは、こちらです！
Now, let's look at the details! First up is this!
『RIONA ON THE ステージタペストリー』！
'Riona On The Stage Tapestry'!
イラストは今回、明春先生にお願いさせていただきました！
For the illustration, we asked Akiharu-sensei this time!
Live2Dのリオナをテーマに描かれたイラストで、とっても可愛いイラストになっているので、タペストリーでぜひ堪能してください！
It's an illustration themed around Live2D Riona and turned out super cute, so please enjoy it on the tapestry!
2つ目は、こちら！ 『リオナとおそろい ネックレス』！
The second item is this! 'Matching Necklace with Riona'!
真ん中には王冠のデザイン、周りには伊咲リオナのロゴが入っています！ シンプルになってますので、ぜひリオナとおそろいにしてくれたら嬉しいです！
It has a crown design in the center and the Isaki Riona logo around it. It's nice and simple, so I'd be happy if you match with me!
次は、こちら！ 『リオナのぬいを入れるポーチ』！
Next up is this! 'Pouch to Put Riona's Plushie In'!
リオナっぽさ全開のぬいポーチになってます！ ぜひ、リオナのぬいをいれてくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
It's a plushie pouch packed with Riona style! I'd be so happy if you put Riona's plushie inside!
ぬい以外に使っても大丈夫だよー！ ポーチになるよー！ そしてそして、最後はこちら！
You can also use it as a pouch for other things! And next, the last item is this!
『くしゃみ連発ぬいキーホルダー』！
'Sneezing Spree Plush Keychain'!
今回、描き下ろしイラストの衣装のぬいぐるみキーホルダーになってます！
It's a plush keychain wearing the costume from the newly drawn illustration!
なんとね、この手の部分をポチッて押すと『ハックション！』って言うので、いっぱい押していっぱい浴びてもらえればと思います！
When you press its hand, it actually says 'Achoo!', so please press it a lot and soak in all the sneezes!
そして改めて、フルセットの方を全部見ていきましょう！ こちら！
And let's take a look at the full set altogether! Here it is!
もりもりだくさん！ もちろん、フルセット購入特典もあります！ こちら！
It's packed with stuff! Of course, there's also a full set purchase bonus! Here it is!
フルセット購入特典の1つ目は、直筆サインと箔押しメッセージ入りのバックステージパス風カードです！
The first full set purchase bonus is a backstage pass style card with a handwritten signature and foil-stamped message!
こちらも明春先生のイラストに、すべて私から1つ1つサインさせていただくので、よかったらぜひ買ってみてください！
It features Akiharu-sensei's illustration, and I'll hand-sign each and every one, so please buy it if you like!
2つ目は、特典ボイス！ 『ライブ前に君と』です！
The second bonus is a special voice track! It's titled 'With You Before the Live'!
ライブ前にこう緊張してへなへなっとなってるリオナを励ますシチュエーションとなっております！ ぜひボイスの方も聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
It's a scenario where you encourage Riona when she gets all nervous before going live! I'd be really happy if you listen to it!
こちらのグッズは21時からカートオープンです！ みんなよかったら、ぜひゲットしてください！
Cart sales for these items open at 21:00! Everyone, please be sure to get them!
そして！ 大事なお知らせが2つ目、あります！ 聴いてください！
And! There's a second important announcement! Please listen!
伊咲リオナの、初！ ソロの新曲が出まーす！ やったー！ タイトルは『Ring my name』です！
Isaki Riona's first original solo song is coming out! Yay! The title is 'Ring my name'!
こちら、私の思いだったり、これから先どうやって進んでいくか、『私は進んでいくぞ！』というのが、おしゃれで洋風にエレガントに表現された曲となっております！
This song elegantly and stylishly expresses my feelings and how I'll keep pushing forward into the future!
こちらセクシーな振り付けもついているので、よかったらそこに注目もしてくださると嬉しいです！
It also features sexy choreography, so I'd be happy if you paid attention to that as well!
このライブが終わった後すぐにMVも公開されますし、24時からデジタルリリースもあるので、ぜひいっぱい聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
Right after this live ends, the MV will be released! And the digital release starts at 24:00, so please give it lots of listens!
やっぱりこの後は新曲やっちゃいますよね！ ということで、やっていくんですけど、その前にちょっと語らせてくださいよ。
Of course, I'm going to perform the new song next! So we'll get to that, but before we do, please let me talk for a bit.
まあね、リオナはまだまだなことがいっぱいあって、叶えたい夢もいっぱいあります！
Well, you know, there's still so much I haven't achieved yet, and so many dreams I want to fulfill!
なので、まだ何も手にしてない私かもしれませんが、一緒についてきてくれたあなたと一緒に、いろんな夢だったり思い出を作っていきたいです！
So I might still be someone who hasn't achieved anything yet, but together with you who followed me here, I want to fulfill dreams and make memories!
絶対！ 後悔はさせないので、これからも私についてきてくれると嬉しいです！ よろしくお願いします！
I promise you won't regret it! I'd be so happy if you continue to follow me! Thank you so much!
そしてこの後は、新曲のお披露目の前に！ ホロライブの先輩方のオリ曲を使ったダンスメドレーをお届けします！
And next, before revealing the new song, I'll deliver a dance medley using original songs by Hololive seniors!
ので、ぜひみてください！
So please be sure to watch!
行くよ！心の準備できた？
Here I go! Are you ready?
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
楽しくなかったら楽しくない
If it's not fun, it's not fun.
Murder is so fucking かわいい
Murder is so fucking kawaii.
死神先生、かなり頼りない
Shinigami-sensei is pretty unreliable.
素敵な Answer
A wonderful answer.
生きてるだけの奴は Ogres
Those who are just living are ogres.
勝手に死んでく 自己消滅
Dying on their own, self-extinction.
死んでんの？ It's Human Nature
Are you dead? It's human nature.
一生楽しもう、死ぬまで
Let's enjoy life for a lifetime, until we die.
DanceMedley -JAZZ DANCE- / Doggy god's street
[Jazz Dance: Doggy god's street]
DanceMedley -BALLET- / シャルイース
[Ballet: Chaconne]
DanceMedley -TAP DANCE- / ビビデバ
[Tap Dance: Bibideba]
ルーバディドゥバディドゥ
Shooba-diba-diba-doo
DanceMedley -GIRL'S HIP HOP-
[Girl's Hip Hop Performance]
Riona in the house
I'm dressed in lace 甘い嘘は act
I'm dressed in lace, sweet lies are an act
囁くの "Want more?"
Whispering, "Want more?"
吐息まで danger
Even my breath is danger
Every step I take 心ごと奪って
Every step I take steals your heart
Velvet shadows call my name 微熱は隠して
Velvet shadows call my name, hiding a slight fever
午前零時
Midnight
今、Veilが解け
Now, the veil is lifted
I'm breaking into the night
まだ夜は醒めやしない
The night is far from over
さあ、誰しもが焦がれるままで
Come on, as everyone yearns
「私を見て...」
"Look at me..."
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it resonate
今から Watch me light
From now on, watch me light
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, when I bloom in full
煌めく Reina
A glittering Reina
指先まで優雅に揺れる
Swaying gracefully to my fingertips
鏡越しの操り人形
A puppet beyond the mirror
壊れそうに微笑んで
Smiling as if about to break
瞳の奥 Fallin' low
Deep in my eyes, fallin' low
唇まで Like it goes
Down to my lips, like it goes
I can't stop 巡る走馬灯
I can't stop, a revolving lantern of memories
さあ、魅せましょう
Now, let me enchant you
綺麗な嘘で
With beautiful lies
着飾らないのマスカレード
In an unadorned masquerade
Go ahead, keep each promise
それならばいっそ Shall we dance?
If so, why not "Shall we dance?"
Come on, say Reina, Reina, Reina!
Flavor, Fly, No answer
今更 Bad mark, 連打 Bot
At this point, bad mark, spamming bot
やってられねーな
Can't stand this crap
I'm a wonder, can't look away, boy
魅せつけるの
I'll show you
全てを賭けて
Staking everything
Click, click, tap, tap, and keep on posing
Flick, flick, snap, snap, and everybody dancing
微熱の中
In the middle of a slight fever,
景色が溶けて
the scenery melts away.
まだ夢は醒めない
The dream hasn't awakened yet.
To younger me, “you're alright”
To younger me, "you're alright."
名もなきあの頃に
Back in those nameless days,
「後悔はない」
"I have no regrets."
Ring my name 響かせろ
Ring my name, make it resound!
今から watch me rise
From now on, watch me rise.
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, if I bloom in full glory,
煌めく Riona
I'll shine brightly, Riona.
明け方まで気高く踊る
Dancing proudly until dawn,
琥珀色のマスカレード
an amber masquerade.
壊れそうに舞い乱れ
Dancing wildly as if I'm about to break.
Viva la reina
Cantad al alba ya
sing to the dawn now.
Viva la reina
Cantad al alba ya
sing to the dawn now.
Ring my name 響かせろ
Ring my name, make it resound!
今から watch me rise
From now on, watch me rise.
泡沫の tiara に
Entranced by an ephemeral tiara,
魅せられ
enchanted,
ただ憧れ
simply longing,
手を伸ばして
reaching out my hand.
これからも私についてきてください！
Please keep following me from now on!
以上、伊咲リオナでした！
That was Isaki Riona!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
響咲リオナ生誕祭 2026
[Isaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026]
お越しいただき、ありがとうございました！！
Thank you so much for coming!!
これからも皆さんとずっと一緒に居たい 貴方の居場所でありたいです！！
I want to stay with you all forever and be a place where you belong!!
お届けしたパフォーマンスが貴方の心に少しでも何かを残せているといいな 本当に本当にありがとう！！
I hope my performance left something in your heart. Thank you so very much!!